The "My Child" website is a password protected portal for parents
"My Child"ウェブサイトは、 パスワードで保護されたポータルで
to view their child's progress while at Bodwell.
保護者がBodwellにいる間の子供の進捗状況を見ることができます
To begin, we recommend Chrome or Safari as the site is optimized for these platforms.
はじめに、このサイトを使用するためのブラウザとして、 ChromeまたはSafariをお勧めします
There are a number of ways to reach the portal. You can go through our website at bodwell.edu
ポータルにアクセスするにはいくつかの方法があります。bodwell.eduのウェブサイトから
and then find the ".community" tab
".community"のタブからアクセスするか
or by typing mychild.bodwell.edu directly into you browser.
ブラウザで直接mychild.bodwell.eduをタイプしウェブページにアクセスすることもできます
To log in, you must have a verified e-mail with the school.
ログインするためには、あらかじめ学校に Eメールアドレスを登録することが必要です
Your log in credentials will be sent to your email and updated each term
あなたのログイン資格はあなたのEメールに送られ、各学期に更新されます
Once logged in, you are taken to the "My Child" dashboard
ログインすると、「マイチャイルド」ダッシュボードに移動します
which is an overview of all of child's information.
これは子どものすべての情報の概要です
There are 7 components to this dashboard.
このダッシュボードには7つのコンポーネントがあります
The 4 tabs at the top; we are currently on the first tab labelled "My Child".
上部には4つのタブがあり、私たちは現在、「私の子供」と名付けられた一番目のタブにいます
Second is your child's information including the house and hall they belong to,
二番目に、あなたの子供 が所属するハウスやホールの情報、
and how long they have been enrolled at Bodwell.
Bodwellでの在学期間です
This section is for general announcements and reminders.
このセクションは、一般的なお知らせとリマインダー用です.
This is the academic overview of your child
こちらははあなたの子供のアカデミックの概要です
You have a quick glance at the current courses, grades well as their attendance.
あなたはここで子供たちの現在のコース、成績、出席率をすばやく確認することができます
A more detailed look at each student's academics can be found under the "Academic Record" tab
各コースの詳細については、今から説明される"Academic Record"タブの下で
explained in a moment
見つけることができます
The next component is a summary of your child's participation hours
次 は、あなたの子供の参加時間の要約です
Again, a more detailed breakdown can be found under the third  tab labelled"Student Life Record".
これも"Student Life Record"という三番目のタブの下により詳細な内訳があります
Below that is a term timeline identifying important dates.
以下は各学期の重要な日付をお知らせ する タイムラインです
You can move forward or backward by using the arrows.
矢印を使って前後に移動することができます
Lastly, a list of staff involved in your child's life at Bodwell.
最後は、ボドウェル在学中にあなたの子供が関係しているスタッフのリストです
The first column is teachers of their academic subjects
最初のコラムはアカデミックのコースを担当している教師陣です
The second is their extra-cirriccular teachers including E-Block, clubs, and teams.
二番目はクラブ活動、スポーツチーム、また放課後活動担当の教師たちです
Third, their counsellors and their advisors.
三番目は、カウンセラーとアドバイザー
Lastly, the principals.
最後は校長です
Back to the tabs, clicking "Academic Record"
タブに戻って、"Academic Record"をクリックすると
will bring you to a more detailed look at your child's courses.
あなたの子供のコースをより詳細に見ることができます
We call this the "Grade Book"
これを"Grade Book"と呼びます
Clicking this box, a list of current courses will drop down.
このボックスをクリックすると、現在のコースのリストがドロップダウンします
The second box on the right will reveal components that will make up the grade
右側の2番目のボックスには、グレードを構成するコンポーネントと
and how it is weighted for the final mark.
最終マークにどのように反映されているかが表示されます
In this example, we can see that assignments are worth 20% of the final grade,
こちらの例では、課題は最終成績の20％、
quizzes 5% and tests 40%.
クイズは5％、テストは40％と評価されていることがわかります
Below we can see the results of each of those components as they happen.
以下では、これらのコンポーネントの結果をその都度確認できます
Results are recorded and posted by teachers as soon as they are completed.
Results are recorded and posted by teachers as soon as they are completed.
The "Student Life Record" is a detailed look at their participation hours.
結果は、完了するとすぐに記録され、教師によってアップロードされます
The first box reveals which term we are looking at
最初のボックスは、チェックしたい学期を選ぶことができます
and the second is the type of participation recorded.
二番目のボックスは参加内容の項目を選ぶことができます
There are 4 types of participation hours
参加時間の項目は４つ、
as well as their volunteer and work experience hours which are required for graduation.
また卒業に必要なボランティアと勤務体験時間もここで見ることができます
Below, all the details for each entry including
下のリストは、どのスタッフが時間を記録したのかなどを含む、
which staff member has logged the hours.
すべての詳細を示します
The last tab is the "Bodwell Explained" tab
最後のタブは、よくある質問や問題のビデオライブラリー、
which is a video library of common questions and issues.
またボドウェルの生徒の生活を垣間見ることもできる
as well as an inside look at a students life here at Bodwell.
"Bodwell Explained"タブです
Videos are divided into two main categories,
動画は主に2つのカテゴリ、
"Academic" and "Student Life" videos.
"Academic"と"Student Life"に分類されます
To begin, simply click on the video or the topic that you are interested in,
まず、ビデオまたは興味のあるトピックをクリックすると
and a video window should pop up.
ビデオウィンドウがポップアップします
Begin by pressing play.
右下の角に字幕 があります
Here, we will make as many languages as possible available.
こちらで様々な言語に対応できるようにします
By clicking on the top right corner you can enter the fullscreen mode.
右上の角をクリックすることでフルスクリーンモードにすることができます
Please exit this mode by pressing "esc".
また、フルスクリーンモードを終了させたい場合は"esc"を押してください
Finally, to return to the main dashboard page,
最後に、メインページに戻りたい場合は
simply click on the "My Child" tab here.
ここの"My Child"タブをクリックしてください
however, it will also refresh the information.
そしてすべての情報も更新されます
If you have any questions or have trouble logging in,
ご不明な点やログインに問題がある場合は
please contact Helpdesk.mychild@bodwell.edu for more information.
Helpdesk.mychild@bodwell.eduまでご連絡ください
Here's how you can add the My Child website to the home screen of your mobile device.
"My Child"ウェブサイトをモバイル・デバイスのホーム画面に追加する方法は次のとおりです
Simply open "My Child" in your browser
まず、"My Child"ウェブサイトを開き、
Click on "options" and click "add to home screen".
"options"をクリックした後、"add to home screen".をクリックします
confirm by pressing "add",
"add"を押して、ホーム画面に追加することを確定させます
And the "My Child" parent portal will appear as an icon on your home screen for easy access.
こうすることで　"My Child"のポータルは簡単にアクセスできるように、ホーム画面にアイコンとして表示されます